A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A81), 1874-2003; 7; 163.49 Cubic Feet 449 containers. Boxes 652-1076; Document boxes 652-1076.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 12.91 Cubic Feet 34 letter document boxes
    - Scholars - Hirsch, Werner Z., 1977-1979 (Box 683, Folder 4520)
    - Scholars - Hondius, Fritz, 1974, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 683, Folder 4521)
    - Scholars - Huffaker, Carl, 1977-1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 684, Folder 4522)
    - Scholars - Jensen, Richard, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4523)
    - Scholars - Kahin, Audrey and George - Joint residency, 1978-1979, 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 684, Folder 4524)
    - Scholars - Kauffman, Stanley, 1977-1981 (Box 684, Folder 4525)
    - Scholars - Kedourie, Elie, 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 684, Folder 4526)
    - Scholars - Kelman, Herbert, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4527)
    - Scholars - Kempe, C. Henry, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4528)
    - Scholars - Kermode, Frank, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4529)
    - Scholars - Kindersley R., 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4530)
    - Scholars - Kornberg, Arthur, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4531)
    - Scholars - Kunin, Calvin M., 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4532)
    - Scholars - Kurzweil, Edith, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 684, Folder 4533)
    - Scholars - Lamb, Hubert H., 1978-1979, 1981-1983 (Box 685, Folder 4534)
    - Scholars - Landes, D.S. (did not go), 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4535)
    - Scholars - Lapidoth, Ruth, 1976-1978, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 685, Folder 4536)
    - Scholars - Lawson, Ruth C., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4537)
    - Scholars - Leendertse, Jan, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4538)
    - Scholars - Leiderman, Hubert, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4539)
    - Scholars - Lein, Allen, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4540)
    - Scholars - Lepawsky, Albert, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4541)
    - Scholars - Libet, Benjamin, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4542)
    - Scholars - Liebaers, Herman, 1977-1981, 1983-1985 (Box 685, Folder 4543)
    - Scholars - Lijphart, Arena (did not go), 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4544)
    - Scholars - Lindblom, C.E. (did not go), 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4545)
    - Scholars - Lipson, Leon, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4546)
    - Scholars - Mackendrick, Paul, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 4547)
    - Scholars - Marder, Arthur, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4548)
    - Scholars - Mayr, Ernst, 1976-1979, 1983, 1989 (Box 686, Folder 4549)
    - Scholars - McLane, Charles B., 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4550)
    - Scholars - McMillan, George, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4551)
    - Scholars - Meiggs, Russell, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4552)
    - Scholars - Miller, George E., 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 686, Folder 4553)
    - Scholars - Miller, Linda B., 1975-1978, 1981, 1989 (Box 686, Folder 4554)
    - Scholars - Morgan, Roger, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4555)
    - Scholars - Morris, Richard B., 1972-1973, 1976-1978, 1981, 1987 (Box 686, Folder 4556)
    - Scholars - Mosher, Frederick, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 4557)
    - Scholars - Mothersill, Mary, 1976-1977, 1981, 1984-1985 (Box 686, Folder 4558)
    - Scholars - Najder, Z., 1976-1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 687, Folder 4559)
    - Scholars - Namias, Jerome, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 687, Folder 4560)
    - Scholars - Nelkin, Dorothy, 1977-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 687, Folder 4561)
    - Scholars - Noack, Paul, 1976-1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 687, Folder 4562)
    - Scholars - O'Gorman (did not go), 1973-1977, 1981 (Box 687, Folder 4563)
    - Scholars - Opoku, 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 687, Folder 4564)
    - Scholars - Patrick, Ruth, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 687, Folder 4565)
    - Scholars - Patrick, Ruth - Supplementary Material, 1/29/79 (Box 687, Folder 4566)
    - Scholars - Paulini, 1976-1977, 1981-1983 (Box 687, Folder 4567)
    - Scholars - Paulson, Ronald, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 687, Folder 4568)
    - Scholars - Perkins, James A., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4569)
    - Scholars - Pessen, Edward, 1977-1979, 1981, 1984 (Box 688, Folder 4570)
    - Scholars - Pierre, Andrew J., 1975-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 688, Folder 4571)
    - Scholars - Pizzorno (did not go), 1978, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4572)
    - Scholars - Price, Jacob M., 1977-1981 (Box 688, Folder 4573)
    - Scholars - Prosterman, Roy L., 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4574)
    - Scholars - Quesada, G. (did not go), 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4575)
    - Scholars - Sister Bernetta Quinn, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4576)
    - Scholars - Rabb, Robert L., 1977-1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 688, Folder 4577)
    - Scholars - Rannit, Aleksis, 1976, 1981 (Box 688, Folder 4578)
    - Scholars - Rawley, James A., 1975-1977, 1981, 1989 (Box 688, Folder 4579)
    - Scholars - Reuber, Grant L., 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 688, Folder 4580)
    - Scholars - Richardson, Joanna, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4581)
    - Scholars - Robinson, Raoul, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4582)
    - Scholars - Rosecrance, Richard, 1976-1977, 1081 (Box 689, Folder 4583)
    - Scholars - Rosenzweig, Robert, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4584)
    - Scholars - Russell, Diane, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4585)
    - Scholars - Rystad, Goram, 1977-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 689, Folder 4586)
    - Scholars - Salem, E.A., 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 689, Folder 4587)
    - Scholars - Scaglione, Aldo, 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4588)
    - Scholars - Schlatter, Richard (did not go), 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4589)
    - Scholars - Scott, Andrew M., 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4590)
    - Scholars - Scott, Anne F., 1976-1987, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4591)
    - Scholars - Schulz, Max F., 1976-1981, 1986 (Box 689, Folder 4592)
    - Scholars - Scruton, Roger, 1976-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 689, Folder 4593)
    - Scholars - Seeman, Melvin, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4594)
    - Scholars - Segal, Lore, 1969, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 689, Folder 4595)
    - Scholars - Shackleford, Rudy, 1976-1977 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4596)
    - Scholars - Shimshoni, Daniel, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 690, Folder 4597)
    - Scholars - Smart, Ian, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 690, Folder 4598)
    - Scholars - Smith, Thomas B., 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4599)
    - Scholars - Snowden, Frank M., Jr., 1976-1978, 1981-1983 (Box 690, Folder 4600)
    - Scholars - Solomon, Barbara M., 1976-1977, 1981, 1985 (Box 690, Folder 4601)
    - Scholars - Sondermann, Fred A. (did not go), 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4602)
    - Scholars - Spiro, Herbert John, 1977-1978, 1981, 1984 (Box 690, Folder 4603)
    - Scholars - Stabenau, James R., 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4604)
    - Scholars - Stone, Lawrence, 1976-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 690, Folder 4605)
    - Scholars - Stourzh, Gerald (did not go), 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4606)
    - Scholars - Strout, Cushing, 1977-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 690, Folder 4607)
    - Scholars - Tannenbaum, Edward, 1977, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4608)
    - Scholars - Thorpe, James, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4609)
    - Scholars - Vermes, Laszlo (did not go), 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 690, Folder 4610)
    - Scholars - Viereck, Peter, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4611)
    - Scholars - Washburn, Wilcomb E., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4612)
    - Scholars - Watson, Barbara B., 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4613)
    - Scholars - Wedin, Walter F., 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4614)
    - Scholars - Wellek, Rene, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4615)
    - Scholars - Wenk, Edward, 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4616)
    - Scholars - Williams, Oliver P., 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4617)
    - Scholars - Williams-Ashman, Howard G., 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4618)
    - Scholars - Winters, Robert W., 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4619)
    - Scholars - Wofford, Harris, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4620)
    - Scholars - Zajonc, Robert B., 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 691, Folder 4621)
    - Small Farms Crops and Animals - Conference, 1977-1983 (Box 691, Folder 4622, Box 692, Folder 4623-4624)
    - Television Programming International Exchange - Conference, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 692, Folder 4625-4627, Box 693, Folder 4628)
    - Transfer of Power in Africa - Conference, 1976-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 693, Folder 4629)
    - University of Michigan - Regional Integration Conference, 1975-1981 (Box 693, Folder 4630)
    - University of Michigan - Regional Integration Conference - Evaluation, 1977, 1980 (Box 693, Folder 4631)
    - Western European Cities - Conference, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 693, Folder 4632)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150; 5.26 Cubic Feet 14 containers
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - United States, 200
      - Chamie, Joseph, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 693, Folder 4633)
      - Chamie, Joseph - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 694, Folder 4634)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - California, 205
      - University of California - Resnikoff, 1971-1976 (Box 694, Folder 4635)
      - University of California - Sabagh, 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 694, Folder 4636)
      - University of California - Sabagh, 1974-1977 (Box 694, Folder 4637)
      - University of California - Sabagh - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 694, Folder 4638)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Connecticut, 208
      - Birdsall, Nancy, 1976-1979 (Box 694, Folder 4639)
      - Birdsall, Nancy - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 694, Folder 4640)
      - Birdsall, Nancy - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 694, Folder 4641)
      - Yale University - Anderson, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 694, Folder 4642)
      - Yale University - Anderson - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 695, Folder 4643)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - District of Columbia, 210
      - Merrick, Thomas W., 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 695, Folder 4644)
      - Merrick, Thomas W. - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 695, Folder 4645)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Illinois, 216
      - Zolberg, Aristide R., 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 695, Folder 4646-4648)
      - Zolberg, Aristide R. - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 695, Folder 4649)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Massachusetts, 224
      - Boston University - Wescott, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 695, Folder 4650)
      - Boston University - Wescott - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 695, Folder 4651)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Michigan, 225
      - University of Michigan - Goldberg, 1974-1979 (Box 696, Folder 4652)
      - University of Michigan - Goldberg - Evaluation, 1974-1977 (Box 696, Folder 4653)
      - University of Michigan - Yengoyan, 1972-1979 (Box 696, Folder 4654)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - New York, 235
      - City University of New York - Muller, 1973-1979, 1981 (Box 696, Folder 4655-4658)
      - City University of New York - Muller - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 697, Folder 4659)
      - City University of New York - Muller - Supplementary Material, 1977 July (Box 697, Folder 4660-4661)
      - Fordham University - Cooney, 1975-1981 (Box 697, Folder 4662-4663)
      - Fordham University - Cooney - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 697, Folder 4664)
      - Miller, Barbara D., 1976-1981 (Box 698, Folder 4665)
      - Miller, Barbara D. - Evaluation, 1977 (Box 698, Folder 4666)
      - Miller, Barbara D. - Supplementary Material, 1978 Dec. 19 (Box 698, Folder 4667)
      - University of Rochester - Ali, 1974-1981 (Box 698, Folder 4668-4669)
      - University of Rochester - Ali - Evaluation, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 698, Folder 4670)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Oklahoma, 239
      - Phillips University - Rhoades, 1975-1981 (Box 699, Folder 4671-4672)
      - Phillips University - Rhoades - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 699, Folder 4673)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Pennsylvania, 241
      - Behrman, Jere Richard, 1976-1981 (Box 699, Folder 4674-4676)
      - Behrman, Jere Richard - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 699, Folder 4677)
      - Pennsylvania State University - Robinson, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 700, Folder 4678)
      - Pennsylvania State University - Robinson - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 700, Folder 4679)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Philippines, 242
      - Del Mundo, Fe, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 700, Folder 4680)
      - Del Mundo, Fe - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 700, Folder 4681)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Virginia, 252
      - Javillonar, Gloria V., 1976-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 700, Folder 4682)
      - Javillonar, Gloria V. - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 700, Folder 4683)
      - Javillonar, Gloria V. - Supplementary Material, 1977 Dec. (Box 700, Folder 4684)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Brazil, 305
      - Carvalho, Jose L., 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 700, Folder 4685)
      - Carvalho, Jose L., 1976-1979 (Box 701, Folder 4686)
      - Carvalho, Jose L. - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 701, Folder 4687)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Colombia, 311
      - Fundación para la Educación Superior - Escobar-Holgun, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 701, Folder 4688-4689)
      - Fundación para la Educación Superior - Escobar-Holgun - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 701, Folder 4690)
      - Fundación para la Educación Superior - Escobar-Holgun - Supplementary Material, 1973-1977 (Box 701, Folder 4691, Box 702, Folder 4692-4693, Box 703, Folder 4694)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Uruguay, 337
      - Frates, Suzana, 1976-1981 (Box 703, Folder 4695)
      - Frates, Suzana - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 703, Folder 4696)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Australia, 410
      - Burnley, I.H., 1975-1981 (Box 703, Folder 4697)
      - Burnley, I.H. - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 703, Folder 4698)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Malaysia, 473
      - University of Science - Deegan, 1975-977, 1979, 1981 (Box 703, Folder 4699)
      - University of Science - Deegan - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 703, Folder 4700)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Sierra Leone, 499
      - Kandeh, Herbert B.S., 1975-1981 (Box 704, Folder 4701-4703)
      - Kandeh, Herbert B.S. - Evaluation, 1976, 1978 (Box 704, Folder 4704)
      - Kandeh, Herbert B.S. - Supplementary Material, 1975, 1978 (Box 704, Folder 4705-4707)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Korea, 613
      - Lee, Sung Jin, 1976-1981 (Box 705, Folder 4708)
      - Lee, Sung Jin - Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 705, Folder 4709)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Indonesia, 652
      - Gadjah Mada University - Masri, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 705, Folder 4710-4711)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Masri - Evaluation, 1975, 1978 (Box 705, Folder 4712)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Masri - Supplementary Material, 1978 (Box 705, Folder 4713)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Turkey, 805
      - Hacettepe University - Gokgol, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 705, Folder 4714)
      - Hacettepe University - Gokgol - Evaluation, 1976-1978 (Box 705, Folder 4715)
      - Hacettepe University - Gokgol - Supplementary Material, 1979 May (Box 706, Folder 4716)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Egypt, 812
      Related Materials
      See also Record Group 5 International Health Board/Division, Series 485.
      - Sarhan, Ahmend E., 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 706, Folder 4717)
      - Sarhan, Ahmend E. - Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 706, Folder 4718)
  - Unemployment and Human Resource Utilization, 152; 0.85 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 legal document box
    - Unemployment and Human Resource Utilization, 1971-1976, 1981 (Box 706, Folder 4719)
    - Unemployment and Human Resource Utilization - Minutes, 1971-1977 (Box 706, Folder 4720)
    - 152: Sierra Leone, 499
      - Njala University College - Spencer, 1973-1976, 1979 (Box 707, Folder 4721-4722)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 155; 18.41 Cubic Feet 46 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
    - Academy for Educational Development - International Negotiation, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 707, Folder 4723)
    - Academy for Educational Development - International Negotiation - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 707, Folder 4724)
    - Academy for Educational Development - International Negotiation - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 707, Folder 4725)
    - American Society of International Law - Inter-American System, 1973-1979, 1981 (Box 707, Folder 4726-4727, Box 708, Folder 4728)
    - American Society of International Law - Inter-American System - Evaluation, 1978-1979 (Box 708, Folder 4729)
    - American Society of International Law - Inter-American System - Supplementary Material, 1973-1978 (Box 708, Folder 4730-4732, Box 709, Folder 4733)
    - Asia Society - Pacific Conference, 1972-1979, 1981 (Box 709, Folder 4734-4737)
    - Asia Society - Pacific Conference - Evaluation, 1974-1980 (Box 709, Folder 4738)
    - Brookings Institution - Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 709, Folder 4739, Box 710, Folder 4740-4741)
    - Brookings Institution - Arab-Israeli Conflict - Evaluation, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 710, Folder 4742)
    - Brookings Institution - Military Policy, 1973-1976, 1978-1979 (Box 710, Folder 4743)
    - City University of New York - Bunche Institute on the UN - Terrorism Conference, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 710, Folder 4744)
    - City University of New York - Bunche Institute on the UN - Terrorism Conference - Evaluation, 1976, 1979 (Box 710, Folder 4745)
    - Columbia University - Foreign Exchange Markets, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 710, Folder 4746-4748)
    - Columbia University - Third World Bargaining Strategies, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 711, Folder 4749-4751)
    - Columbia University - Third World Bargaining Strategies - Evaluation, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 711, Folder 4752)
    - Columbia University - Third World Bargaining Strategies - Supplementary Material, 1976 Dec. (Box 711, Folder 4753)
    - Conant, Melvin, 1976-1981 (Box 711, Folder 4754-4756)
    - Conant, Melvin - Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1985, 1987 (Box 711, Folder 4757)
    - Conant, Melvin - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978 (Box 712, Folder 4758-4761)
    - Cornell University - Foreign Economic Policies Conference, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 712, Folder 4762)
    - Cornell University - Foreign Economic Policies Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1981 (Box 712, Folder 4763)
    - Falk, Richard A., 1976-1981 (Box 712, Folder 4764)
    - Falk, Richard A. - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 713, Folder 4765)
    - Falk, Richard A. - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 713, Folder 4766)
    - Georgetown University - Arab/Moslem Security and Africa, 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 713, Folder 4767)
    - Georgetown University - Arab/Moslem Security and Africa - Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 713, Folder 4768)
    - Goldaber, Irving, 1969-1979, 1981 (Box 713, Folder 4769-4770)
    - Goldaber, Irving - Evaluation, 1976-1981 (Box 713, Folder 4771)
    - Harvard University - Transnational Conflicts, 1973-1981 (Box 713, Folder 4772)
    - Institute on Man and Science - Nuclear Energy Conference, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 714, Folder 4773)
    - Institute on Man and Science - Nuclear Energy Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1984 (Box 714, Folder 4774)
    - International Energy Associates Limited - Breeder Reactors, 1976-1981 (Box 714, Folder 4775-4778, Box 715, Folder 4779-4781)
    - International Energy Associates Limited - Breeder Reactors - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 715, Folder 4782)
    - International Energy Associates Limited - Breeder Reactors - Supplementary Material, 1978 May (Box 715, Folder 4783-4784, Box 716, Folder 4785-4786)
    - International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study - Climate Modification, 1973-1978, 1981 (Box 716, Folder 4787-4789)
    - International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study - Climate Modification - Evaluation, 1973-1979, 1981 (Box 716, Folder 4790)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies - Conference, 1976, 1979, 1981 (Box 717, Folder 4791)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies - Conference - Evaluation, 1976, 1980 (Box 717, Folder 4792)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies - Maddox, 1974-1979, 1981 (Box 717, Folder 4793-4794)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies - Maddox - Evaluation, 1974-1977 (Box 717, Folder 4795)
    - International Peace Academy - Disarmament Conference, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 717, Folder 4796)
    - International Peace Academy - Disarmament Conference - Evaluation, 1978-1979, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 4797)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1975-1981 (Box 717, Folder 4798, Box 718, Folder 4799)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 718, Folder 4800)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978 (Box 718, Folder 4801-4803)
    - Johns Hopkins University - U.S. and the U.N., 1975-1981 (Box 718, Folder 4804-4806)
    - Latin American Studies Association Conference, 1977-1981 (Box 719, Folder 4807)
    - Latin American Studies Association Conference - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 719, Folder 4808)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - American-German Energy Conference, 1976-1981 (Box 719, Folder 4809)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - American-German Energy Conference - Evaluation, 1976-1979, 1986 (Box 719, Folder 4810)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - American-German Energy Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977 (Box 719, Folder 4811-4812)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Energy Resources Works, 1973-1978, 1981 (Box 719, Folder 4813-4814, Box 720, Folder 4815-4817)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Energy Resources Works - Evaluation, 1973-1977, 1979 (Box 720, Folder 4818)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Energy Resources Works - Supplementary Material, 1974-1977 (Box 720, Folder 4819-4820, Box 721, Folder 4821-4824, Box 722, Folder 4825-4826)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Global Monitoring, 1975-1981 (Box 722, Folder 4827-4828)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Global Monitoring - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 722, Folder 4828A)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Global Monitoring - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 723, Folder 4829)
    - Middle East Institute - North Sinai-Gaza Development, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 723, Folder 4830-4831)
    - Middle East Institute - North Sinai-Gaza Development - Evaluation, 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 723, Folder 4832)
    - Mississippi State University - Radvanyi, 1973-1978, 1980 (Box 723, Folder 4833)
    - Mississippi State University - Radvanyi - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 723, Folder 4834)
    - Mississippi State University - Radvanyi - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 723, Folder 4835)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Global Environmental Monitoring System Conference, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 724, Folder 4836-4838)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Global Environmental Monitoring System Conference - Evaluation, 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 724, Folder 4839)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Global Environmental Monitoring System Conference - Supplementary Material, 1973 (Box 724, Folder 4840)
    - National Planning Association - Canadian-American Relation, 1975-1979, 1981 (Box 724, Folder 4841-4842)
    - National Planning Association - Canadian-American Relation - Evaluation, 1975-1979 (Box 724, Folder 4843)
    - New York University - Walter, 1973-1977, 1981 (Box 724, Folder 4844-4845)